Class of 1927 Records, 1923-ongoing
Smith College Archives
Class of 1927, Records
1923-ongoing
Smith College. Class of 1927
RG 80 UUID:4692216e-8ae8-439f-97f1-c878e2894983
9 boxes (3.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
The Class of 1927 was the forty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1927 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1927, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
The Class of 1927 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speech - Rev. Harry Emerson Fosdick 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 5)
- Freshman Frolic 1923 (Box 1985, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind 1923 (Box 1985, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1923-1924 (Box 1985, Folder 8)
- Fund Letters 1957-1973 (Box 1985, Folder 9)
- General 1923-1927 (Box 1985, Folder 10)
- Groups - Photographs 1923-1927 (Box 1985, Folder 11)
- Hoop Rolling 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 14)
- Last Sing 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 15)
- Class Letters 1929-1992 (Box 1985, Folder 16)
- Necrology 1981 (Box 1985, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1985, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1985, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1932 (Box 1985, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1937 (Box 1985, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 1985, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 1985, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 1986, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 1986, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 1986, Folder 3)
- Reunions - Reunion Chair's Notebook 1962 (Box 1986, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 1986, Folder 5)
- Reunions - Reunion Chair's Notebook 1967 (Box 1987, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 1987, Folder 2)
- Reunions - Questionnaire 1972 (Box 1987, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1977 (Box 1987, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 1987, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 1987, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 1987, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1997 (Box 1987, Folder 8)
- Reunions 2002 (Box 1987, Folder 9)
- Reunions - Memorabilia undated (Box 1987, Folder 10)
- Reunions - Photographs undated (Box 1987, Folder 11)
- Reunions - Songs 1932-72 (Box 1987, Folder 12)
- Scrapbook 1947-55 (Box 1987, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Biographical Notes and Clippings undated (Box 1987, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Records 1927 (Box 1987, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics 1927 (Box 1987.1, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics - Photographs 1927 (Box 1987.1, Folder 2)
- Songs undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 3)
- Sophomore Carnival 1925 (Box 1987.1, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Push 1925 (Box 1987.1, Folder 5)
- Step Sings undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 6)
- Class Supper undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 7)
- Class Treasurer's Records undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 8)
- Class Treasurer's Card Files, Class Secretary's Card Files undated (Box CB)
- Scrapbook 1947-1955 (Box OV)
- Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)